keeko.com 2013-03-13

# Privacy Policy - Keeko

First, Keeko is here to provide a free online service platform that Twitter, Tumblr, LinkedIn and Google plus users can leverage to grow their reach in the social media sphere. It is a peaceful social media exchange community. It is just right that in return, you do your part of maintaining and protecting the integrity of the website. 

Second, Keeko acknowledges the importance of protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to Keeko.com and its mother company, Clicking Labs with respect to all products and services provided on the platform. In addition, this policy also applies to provider of Keeko, yourself and other users of Keeko. By using the Keeko website, you consent to the collection, usage and disclosure of data described in this policy. 

Please read the following statements in this policy to understand our practices regarding your personal data and how we use it to the benefit of the whole Keeko community.

## What Information Do We Collect

We collect, store and use identifiable information that includes but not limited to name, date of birth, gender, business industry, contact information, email addresses, telephone numbers; demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests, website profile information and other additional personal and non-personal information. You voluntarily provide this information at the time of registration, subscription and filling out forms for survey purposes or if you contact us. 

We may also collect, store and use information about your visits (traffic data, location data, weblogs) and details of your use of the website (online social connections made through Keeko); when you enter a competition, promotion, report a problem. We may also store your Twitter, Tumblr, LinkedIn and Google plus profile information provided to us through the platforms' respective API with your express permission.

Other automatically collected information includes type and version of web browser used, operating system, IP address, domain names, access times, list of URLs starting with referring site addresses, activity on Keeko and the site you exit to.

This information is used for the general operation of the service and to provide statistics regarding the use of Keeko website. 

**Note:** Keeko encourages you to review the privacy policies of websites you link to through the Keeko service to understand how they collect, use and share your information. Keeko is not responsible for content and privacy statements outside of the website.

## How we use your information

Personal information submitted and collected will be used for purposes specified in this privacy statement. Keeko may use your data to:

  1. improve your website experience 
  2. send information to you that, at our discretion, may be of interest to you by post, email or of similar channel. 
  3. send marketing communications in connection to our services or of carefully selected third parties Keeko trust that may be of interest to you by post, email or of similar channels ;Inform us anytime if you no longer wish to receive marketing communications so we can send you opt-out links included on our email communications.
  4. contact you via surveys to conduct research about opinion and feedback regarding current services and/or of potential new services that we may consider offering
  5. carry out our obligation of providing the full range of our services 
  6. inform you of interactive features of our service that you may wish to participate
  7. notify you about changes to our services

We will not provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing without your express consent.

## Information Disclosure

Keeko does not sell, rent or lease customer lists to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information in line with the following reasons.

  1. In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets
  2. If we are under the duty to disclose information in compliance to any legal obligations and/or to enforce our terms and policies
  3. If Keeko and all its assets are acquired by a third party
  4. If the need arise to protect and defend the rights and property of Keeko
  5. If we need to protect the personal safety of Keeko users or the public
  6. If trusted partners need help to perform statistical analysis, in which case we may send you an email, postal mail, customer support or arrange for deliveries. 

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties and will adhere to maintaining the confidentiality of your information.

## Use of Cookies

We may collect information about your general internet usage such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of pageviews by using a cookie file.

What is a cookie file? It's a text file sent by a web server to a web browser to be stored. The text file is sent back to the server every time the browser requests a page from the server. Thus, cookies enable the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use cookies to improve the website's usability and to personalize your online experience. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, however, you are allowed to refuse or decline cookies. This will, unfortunately, render some website features non-functional, which will deny you to experience the services to its fullest. Some cookies are essential for the site to operate, such as the cookies used to identify users when they log in.

When you sign up on Keeko and sign in with your Twitter, Tumblr, Google plus, LinkedIn account, you are already giving permission to the use of cookies. However, we have no control over our advertisers that also use cookies.

## Security of Your Personal Data

Keeko secures your personal information and takes reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration of your data as well as unauthorized access, use or disclosure from outside parties. 

However, with the inherently unsecure data transmission on the internet, Keeko cannot guarantee security of data sent over the web. In addition, you are responsible for keeping your access (username and password) confidential. 

## Policy Changes

In the event that we make changes on our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 28 February 2013

## Contact Us

Questions, comments, requests, feedback, etc. regarding the privacy policy are welcome. Please feel free to contact is through our website <http://www.keeko.com/>.
